Of course, be a pre-vile.
I have a concern.
You have your own concern.
Second.
Roll call.
Johnson.
Lewis.
Question.
Four, sir.
Hi.
I have number six, resolution authorizing the sale.
Issuants in delivery of certificates of indebtedness.
Of the authority to provide funds to refinance certain outstanding indebtedness of the authority.
Authorizing sale, they're up at a discount and waving competitive bidding they're on.
Being, this is the same item as on the council.
Correct.
So, same details as we talked about earlier.
Do we have a motion to approve the resolution?
Looks to prove.
And a second.
Second.
Roll call.
Question.
Johnson.
Four, sir.
Lewis.
Hi.
I have number seven.
It's trustee community announcements.
Item number eight is adjourned.
We have a motion to adjourn.
Motion to adjourn.
Second.
Roll call.
Four, sir.
Hi.
Lewis.
Question.
All right.